[{
        "question": "What's the title of this song?",
        "correct": "Purple Rain",
        "incorrect1": "",
        "incorrect2": "",
        "incorrect3": "",
        "src": "audio/predit.ogg"
    },

    {
        "question": "Who wrote this song?",
        "correct": "Don't Stop Believing",
        "incorrect1": "",
        "incorrect2": "",
        "incorrect3": "",
        "src": "audio/journeyedit.ogg"
    },

    {

        "question": "What's the title of this song?",
        "correct": "Panama",
        "incorrect1": "",
        "incorrect2": "",
        "incorrect3": "",
        "src": "audio/panamaedit.ogg"
    },


    {

        "question": "Who wrote this song?",
        "correct": "Madness - Our House",
        "incorrect1": "",
        "incorrect2": "",
        "incorrect3": "",
        "src": "audio/ourhouseedit.ogg"

    },

    {

        "question": "What's the title of this song?",
        "correct": "Another One bites the dust",
        "incorrect1": "",
        "incorrect2": "",
        "incorrect3": "",
        "src": "audio/aobtdedit.ogg"

    },

    {

        "question": "Who wrote this song?",
        "correct": "Africa",
        "incorrect1": "",
        "incorrect2": "",
        "incorrect3": "",
        "src": "audio/africaedit.ogg"
    },


    {

        "question": "What's the title of this song?",
        "correct": "Mr. Mister - Broken Wings",
        "incorrect1": "",
        "incorrect2": "",
        "incorrect3": "",
        "src": "audio/brokenwingsedit.ogg"

    },

    {

        "question": "Who wrote this song?",
        "correct": "You give love a bad name",
        "incorrect1": "fake",
        "incorrect2": "fake",
        "incorrect3": "fake",
        "src": "audio/bonjoviedit.ogg"

    },

    {

        "question": "What's the title of this song?",
        "correct": "Faith - George Michael",
        "incorrect1": "fake",
        "incorrect2": "fake",
        "incorrect3": "fake",
        "src": "audio/faithedit.ogg"

    },

    {

        "question": "Who wrote this song?",
        "correct": "Welcome to the Jungle",
        "incorrect1": "fake",
        "incorrect2": "fake",
        "incorrect3": "fake",
        "src": "audio/jungleedit.ogg"
    }
]
